http://www.nakedmtnwinery.com/privacy-policy

Purchase
Privacy Policy Naked Mountain Winery is committed to respecting your privacy. We will not sell, rent, loan, share, or transfer any personal information regarding our visitors to any unrelated third parties without your consent. Reasonable care is used with any information you provide to us and the information will not be used in ways to which you have not consented. However, we may disclose your personal information under limited circumstances if we conclude that we are required by law or have a good faith belief that access, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to protect the rights, property or safety of our winery, its customers or the public. When you register, place an order or provide your personal information to us for any other business purpose, we may collect your name, address, email address, birth date, phone number and credit card information. We may also request additional information. We use this information to process your requests and to communicate with you about your orders. From time to time, we may use your name and contact information to notify you of changes to the web site, new releases, special offers and events we think you’ll find valuable. To prevent receiving this information via any medium, please send a postcard with all the names, addresses and emails you’d like removed from our mailing list toNaked Mountain WineryPO Box 115Markham, Virginia 22643Our winery will track visits to the pages and links on our websites so we can make decisions about the design and usage of the website. While we may choose to share aggregate information on consumer behavior to third parties, none of these statistics contain personally identifying information.Our websites use cookies to identify our registered members when they return to the site. “Cookies” are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive. Our cookies enable us to provide special features such as storing items in your shopping cart between visits. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but most allow you to prevent that by making a change to the browser options. Even without a cookie, you can still use most of the features in our store, including placing items in your shopping cart and purchasing them.By using our website, you consent to the policies described in this privacy statement. The provisions of this policy are subject to change and any changes to this privacy policy will be posted on this page.If you have any questions, comments, or concerns regarding this website and our stated policy, please feel free to contact us.Naked Mountain Winery2747 Leeds Manor RoadMarkham, Virginia 22643t: (540) 364-1609e: drinknaked@nakedmtnwinery.com
SubscribeEnter your email below to be added to our mailing list.
Email
*
Thank you!
Back to Top
Privacy Policy© Naked Mountain Winery & Vineyards
